(Leonard:)The viewing area's right over there.
Sheldon, your girl... Date... Person...
Ramona's here.
- Oh, hello.
- Oh, sorry I'm late.
I got caught up reading the draft
of your latest paper.
Did you enjoy the footnote where
I illustrate mirror symmetry by likening it...
(Sheldon:)- ...to The Flash playing tennis with himself?
- So funny.
[LAUGHS]
(Ramona:)The idea that you might be able
to incorporate gravity...
(Ramona:)...I have to tell you,
I found it physically exhilarating.
(Sheldon:)My hypotheses tend to have that effect.
(Ramona:)I'm sorry I didn't bring enough
for your friends.
(Ramona:)I assumed we were going to be alone.
(Leonard:)Oh. Yeah. No, we were just going.
(Howard:)To watch, right?
- No. Come on now. We're going out.
- Oh, come on. We'll be quiet.
Come on, let's go.
(Leonard:)Okay, you two.
You just have a nice whatever this is.